Okay. So we have the results back.
It’s moved it 3% from 87% to 90%.
Right now it's a combination of everybody just writing their own skills, right?
Skills are a little bit personal, right?
You prompt your LLM like your coding agent, like you do a session.
At the end of the session, you want to have this repeatable thing, right?
So you say, okay, just save it.
Save it as a skill.
So I was walking through the expo hall.
AI Engineer in San Francisco, and I saw this
brilliant, pure light and I was blinded by it.
And I looked up and it was Chris walking towards me,
and he said, Simon, I need you to evaluate a skill of mine.
And I said, Chris, what skills have you got?
And you said, I have no idea.
So what we're going to do?
This is Chris. Hello. What do you do at Snyk?
I head product strategy at Snyk.
Product strategy at Snyk.
That is indeed the case. That sounds very important.
That maybe.
I would have thought, like
they would need to find someone smarter than you to do that role, though.
Simon left, unfortunately.
And now there's no more smart people.
Okay, because you were the last one. You were the last one.
But you're a good alternative.
That's fine, that's fine.
So, Chris.
Okay, what we do is we're gonna go to GitHub.
We're going to go to Snyk. Yep.
We're going to let's search for a skill.
For a SKILL.md let's find us up and
let's search for a SKILL.md yep.
Let's find something that we're going to
we're going to we're going to evaluate okay.
And run a review.
Okay.
There is one the MCP skill.
This one.
Yeah. This is for creating targets.
So it's our dynamic kind of scanning testing security testing product.
And it's a it's API first.
So we created these skills to help our customers
add targets to to the product okay using cloud. So
let's come here.
Let's make a directory called Snyk Skills.
Then I'm going to I'm going to get clone this fella here.
And then we'll CD into Snyk MCP.
And I'm going to run
agent in here. It's very exciting.
Tessl: not found. Look at that.
Look at that.
Okay. Right.
So we're gonna run Tessl agent here.
And I'm going to say, okay, let's let's say
please, please, we don't know how long we're going to be above agents for.
So it's important to be polite in the run up.
I know, I. Just know. I know I'm doing the same thing.
I'm doing the same thing just in case they take over.
Right? Just
they got good memories. They got there.
They got their goals.
Please take a look in this project.
In fact, let's have a look in this project and and tell me
which skills exist.
Okay.
Let's look at there's just that one.
Or if there's multiple I'm going to yolo this.
There we go.
So that is your agent.
That is the agent that you build. Your this is the Tessl agent.
So it's agent which essentially is
like we got two there.
It's an agent that essentially is there ready.
I tell you it's dedicated to making sure
you're you're agent enablement is as good as it can be.
Okay.
Looking at looking at optimizing the skills and the environment
that you have from a contact point of view.
But it also works a little bit more to getting you to the next stages.
Small step by small step into into closer to a software factory.
Awesome.
Okay so we have two here.
We have, we have the Snyk, the Snyk target, the Snyk API target configuration
I know we have. It's the same thing.
Same thing.
So let's see.
No. So web. So web. And so.
One is for API target.
So this is basically for testing APIs and testing web applications.
So one of them is kind of configuring the test for the web target.
So like if you have like an application to test like a web URL.
Right. So that's that's one skill.
And the other skill is just like if you have an API to test
and you want to send kind of like dynamically test the API for security.
So that's the other skew. So there are two skills here.
So which one do you want to which one should we evaluate.
Let's do the API one. Let's let's see what happens.
Let's let's see what happens.
Target configuration skill.
We'll say use the
Simon workspace.
Right.
So what this is going to do is it's going to run.
Hopefully it will run.
Tessl review run.
And what tessl review run does in fact looking at tessl review help there.
And then it's going to right there it is.
It's run tessl review run okay.
It's running it against the Snyk API target configuration.
And what this is going to do
is it's going to run a review which is an agent review.
So it kicks off a review LLM as a judge style.
It looks at the it looks at the best practices from Anthropic.
And it will say how close, how how well is this skill
been written okay compared to the Anthropic best practices?
Okay.
Now that's not to say that the Anthropic best practices are absolutely perfect.
So if you get 0% here, it might just be that the Anthropic best practice rubbish.
Okay, maybe maybe maybe.
Maybe I'm using it as a caveat
just because we don't know what's going to come back here.
So I'm using that as a caveat.
Okay.
Whatever the score is, we should be able to do a fix
and we should be able to say, how can we improve this.
And so we'll have a look at it and see where we can change the improve.
Well hopefully it's not 100 then because then there's nothing to improve.
But let's.
See what okay.
This is you're in yourself up for a full here.
Hopefully it's not 100. We'll see. We'll see.
I'll tell you what. If it's 100 okay.
You give me some swap. What do you want to bet?
If it's 100, you can have this Tessl swag dallying.
Okay, okay, so.
How about we swap?
Okay, so if it's if it's.
Less hundred, I'll take your heart.
Okay. If it is 100, you can have. Okay.
I mean I mean I mean ideal deal.
You should have said I've just seen the score.
I saw this call as well.
Okay, let's take a look.
So the score is actually to know what 8077.
That's pretty good.
That's pretty good. That's pretty good.
Now let's have a look at where.
So it's already a strong usable skill.
So let me just let me just grab this.
Sorry I got the hat as well.
There we go okay.
I mean that's a good trade.
That's a good trade.
So this is already well your heads your head's pretty big.
That's pretty big Chris I'll I'll take that off
for for many reasons, but I'll put it there for now.
This is already a strong, usable skill.
There you are like that.
It has clear routing API target only.
Good sibling skill disambiguation.
This is super important.
Okay, so you've got two skills.
And it's important to be able to determine when to use one.
When to use the other. Yeah yeah.
And this is very often when we talk about activation. Right.
One of the biggest problems
of of agent activation isn't just do I use your skill or not.
It's do I use the right skill.
And I've got a combination of multiple skills to pick
that's actually really useful.
Yeah.
Good hand
duplicate target warning strong actionable authentic authentication examples.
That's great. That's great.
The skill is too dense, too much detailed authentication reference in line
with the SKILL.md making it less concise and less progressively disclosed.
Okay, so what that means is a skill doesn't get fully loaded normally, okay.
It gets progressively disclosed. Okay.
So you load pieces of a skill at a time.
So what it's probably going to suggest is you take a lot of that skill
and break it into sub files and reference those different subtitles, okay.
And then when the agent realizes I want to go deeper into here,
it'll load that and it doesn't need to, it won't load that.
So it avoids context bloat. Right.
So this is basically this progressive disclosure stuff like content bloat okay.
Content progressive disclosure is two out of three.
Conciseness probably from the size of the skill. Right.
So this tends to be tends to be that of specificity.
One of the hardest words to say in the.
I cannot pronounce it. I'm Polish.
No one actually knows what that means.
It's a true story.
No one. No one knows. Many.
Many, many studied it.
Many people stay studied this word.
But no, no, no one knows.
So we'll just say it's two out of three,
but we don't know how to fix it because we don't know what it means.
Right? There's a bunch of recommended fixes.
What we're going to do because we're agentic developers, okay.
Because we're going to ignore it. We're going to ignore it.
And we're just going to say run Tessl
review, fix.
And we're just going to assume.
Okay. That the fix is are good. Oh, okay.
And we'll apply those fixes and we'll blindly okay.
So basically I'm trusting Tessl to to to do that and just push to production.
Yeah yeah.
Perfect man I'm only I'm only I'm only in on a like just just just go.
Let's just. Let's just. Do it.
Well what we're going to do is we'll show a diff afterwards
and we'll see what it's changed. It's not. Quite that.
Okay. We'll see what it's changed and we can accept.
Or can we, can we have an agent to see the deep.
So I mean like I just go and.
What we'll do, we'll get to do a get this. Okay. Yeah.
You mean get an agent to review. Exactly. Like. Like.
One agent is just doing the fix.
The other can just do the diff review.
Right, and we can go for a beer.
You had me. Let's go for a bit, so that's fine. That's perfect.
So let's have a look. Where where was that?
Can you remember Snyk API web maybe.
I don't remember man config.
It was config skills. There we go. There we go. Yeah.
And it was the API target.
And oh there's a single SKILL.md.
This is the problem. Yeah. It's just bloated like it's.
Too long.
So what I suspect is it's going to do is it's going to reduce this and you'll,
you'll see extra files. Right.
That's what I suspect.
But we'll see because what happens is it tends to read too much of this,
too much of this. Right.
It might update the description as well.
We'll see.
Because very often the name and description of the two pieces
that the agent reads before knowing when to activate the full screen.
Right. So we'll we'll see what happens.
So how do you how do you folks use
obviously thanks to Snyk as well because we use Snyk within Tessl
to to test every single skill that we have on the registry.
From a security point of view, that's true.
But how do you use Tessl?
How do you use skills internally?
Internally?
So I think right now it's a combination of everybody just writing their own skills.
Right. Skills are a little bit personal. Right.
So like, you know like you do like you you you prompt your your your your LLM
like your coding agent, like you do a session at the end of the session.
You want to have this repeatable thing, right?
So you say, okay, just save it.
Save it as a skill. Right.
So can you have your personal skills.
Just kind of one thing that we do, the other thing that we do,
we try to slowly, slowly standardize across the organization.
So kind of share these skills with other people. Right.
And also standardize on some skills.
So for example, if there is a skill that knows
how to push stuff to production,
we want to have like that part of our platform team publishes a skill
that developers can use, because
then it can pass all of the security and quality kind of requirements.
Right.
So like if I were developers,
kind of write a skill to push the production themselves,
it's like a little bit of a freaking out our security team.
Yeah. So like we're doing these two two things broadly.
Right. Like internally how we use skills. Yeah. Yeah.
And let's talk about actually
there's the what was the report that you that you did.
It was toxic skills. Toxic skills. Yeah. Toxic skills.
It's amazing to see how many skills
through kind of just like a core poor wording
for writing actually introduce potential security issues.
Right.
Prompt injection, those types of things. Right.
What can people do differently to actually write skills that are closer to,
you know,
having fewer or no security issues?
I mean, you right.
This is just Tessl. This one.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll tell you what gets it to 100%.
I keep the hat.
If it's not just what that.
We saw back now I know back, but
I want to keep the hat. Okay.
I mean, you know, you said Snyk.
We have.
And so you can run the Snyk tool independently though, right.
So you can run it right at the command line.
We have, we have a tool called Agent Scan.
So that tool is available on GitHub GitHub Snyk
agent scan I think is the is the is the repository there.
And you can just go
there, run the tool, point it at it kind of scans your file system.
But you can also pointed at a skill and you will give you
like a security kind of advisory view of, of that skill.
Right.
So that's for the skills that you write yourself,
but also very important for third party skills
because kind of like this third party skills might be malicious.
Yeah. Right.
So yeah.
So so that's that's recommended for sure.
Yeah. Yeah.
So I think that's, that's that's the main thing really for kind of skill security.
There will be a different categories of,
of problems for first party skills and third party skills.
So I think this space is still evolving.
So we still need to understand what advice to give to developers
who are developing their own skills on kind of security.
Right.
Like that's, that's, that's
a, that's
maybe a bigger problem to solve than just kind of
looking for prompt injections which are malicious.
That's, that's, that's a little bit easier.
But yeah like a work in progress. But we'll get there. There.
Yeah. Yeah.
Cool cool.
okay. So we have the results back.
So it's only moved it plus 3% I'm still going to wear this.
Then it's moved at 3% from 87 to 90.
And it reached that it reached the target score of 90.
Let's have a look. Acting on the judges content.
Judges suggestions I've moved for detailed API authentication method.
Code blocks out of SKILL.md into the new references.
So it has moved that right.
So it's fled the scaling to a smaller pieces.
So now one of the big changes is it will now progressively
disclose that to the agent as and when it needs those specific pieces.
Right. Right. So that's the kind of big one.
And there's a whole bunch of there's a whole bunch of changes here that you'll
that you'll actually see.
So first have a look at this. Now.
Now we've got this references here.
And you'll see extra hosts log out text sequence formatting.
And you've also got the SKILL.md that at this stage will almost certainly.
Yeah it's much smaller.
Yeah. On this one.
No sorry. It's this one. This one. Yeah.
This one's the one I wanted.
It's got the api-authentication.md.
And in here you'll
at some point reached out to that
hasn't as much as I thought I was probably expecting it
to be to be more full for the full code for each authentication method.
Go and have a look at this.
And so it reaches out.
And maybe, maybe if we were to run a couple more times
it would probably actually, you know, do that again right.
Yeah. We still have 10% to go. Right. So yeah. Yeah.
And that's the thing. Right.
Because sometimes we can then have a look at what, what else
it wants to improve and see if it does want to improve and iterate across.
But hey not too bad. Not too bad.
That's great. That's great. That's great. Help.
Yeah I'm gonna use that now.
Yeah. Especially as I need to share my skills.
You know, I don't know if there are any good.
So like like, you know, like,
if it's my personal skills, like, maybe that's fine, right.
But I want to share with my team,
you know, I want I want to do something like that.
And you can add this into,
you know, right into the, into the, into the pull request checks.
And so as soon as a pull request happens, when you still MD, you can rerun
the review, make sure it's not regressing and then types of things.
And it's available for free for developers.
Available for free. So you can you can you can try it out.
You can get you can get an account straight away.
And you have a number of credits on your free
on your kind of like free account.
And then you can just use that throughout the month
and it gets replenished every month.
So amazing.
Amazing awesome. Thank you. Absolute pleasure.
Thank you.
Thank you for joining us.
And and you can have that 3% for free.
You can take that away with you.
Yeah. Thank you very much. Thank you for the hat as well.
Thank you. Yeah. Cheers. Thank you. Cheers.